{
    "level": "level1",
    "instructions": "Congratulations on your new learning endeavor! Here are a few pointers to help you on your journey. First, it is important to recognize that IPA symbols are always presented in brackets. Secondly, each symbol in brackets represents an exact sound. Your job is to learn those sounds. Read the bracketed symbols out loud, keeping the English language in mind. Next, try to guess the English transcription. Type your answer and submit. Once you have feedback on your answer, begin to deconstruct the sounds and commit them to memory before moving on. You will be surprised at how quickly you will learn IPA in this immersive way. Be sure to finish the entire level to log your earned points for a competitive place on the leaderboards!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionNum": 1,
            "question": "[kæt]",
            "answer": "cat"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 2,
            "question": "[hæt]",
            "answer": "hat"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 3,
            "question": "[hit]",
            "answer": "heat"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 4,
            "question": "[sɪt]",
            "answer": "sit"
        },        
        {
            "questionNum": 5,
            "question": "[sɪŋ]",
            "answer": "sing"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 6,
            "question": "[klɪŋ]",
            "answer": "cling"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 7,
            "question": "[fid]",
            "answer": "feed"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 8,
            "question": "[wɪn]",
            "answer": "win"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 9,
            "question": "[kiz]",
            "answer": "keys"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 10,
            "question": "[heɪl]",
            "answer": "hail"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 11,
            "question": "[feɪs]",
            "answer": "face"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 12,
            "question": "[weɪk]",
            "answer": "wake"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 13,
            "question": "[ɛlf]",
            "answer": "elf"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 14,
            "question": "[bæd]",
            "answer": "bad"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 15,
            "question": "[strit]",
            "answer": "street"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 16,
            "question": "[stɛp]",
            "answer": "step"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 17,
            "question": "[mil]",
            "answer": "meal"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 18,
            "question": "[gis]",
            "answer": "geese"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 19,
            "question": "[geɪm]",
            "answer": "game"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 20,
            "question": "[dɛk]",
            "answer": "deck"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 21,
            "question": "[pɪn]",
            "answer": "pin"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 22,
            "question": "[blæst]",
            "answer": "blast"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 23,
            "question": "[dreɪn]",
            "answer": "drain"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 24,
            "question": "[hæk]",
            "answer": "hack"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 25,
            "question": "[greɪt]",
            "answer": "great"
        }
    ]
}
{
    "level": "level2",
    "instructions": "Congratulations! You completed level 1! Follow the same winning process for Level 2. Be sure to finish the entire level to log your earned points for a competitive place on the leaderboards!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionNum": 1,
            "question": "[pul]",
            "answer": "pool"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 2,
            "question": "[ʃu]",
            "answer": "shoe"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 3,
            "question": "[pʊl]",
            "answer": "pull"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 4,
            "question": "[ʃoʊ]",
            "answer": "show"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 5,
            "question": "[bʊk]",
            "answer": "book"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 6,
            "question": "[trʌk]",
            "answer": "truck"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 7,
            "question": "[rud]",
            "answer": "rude"
        },        
        {
            "questionNum": 8,
            "question": "[lʊk]",
            "answer": "look"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 9,
            "question": "[ˈstʌn.ɪŋ]",
            "answer": "stunning"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 10,
            "question": "[sun]",
            "answer": "soon"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 11,
            "question": "[kroʊ]",
            "answer": "crow"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 12,
            "question": "[brɛθ]",
            "answer": "breath"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 13,
            "question": "[θroʊ]",
            "answer": "throw"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 14,
            "question": "[goʊt]",
            "answer": "goat"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 15,
            "question": "[fɑnd]",
            "answer": "fond"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 16,
            "question": "[tɔt]",
            "answer": "taught"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 17,
            "question": "[ˈɑl.ɪv]",
            "answer": "olive"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 18,
            "question": "[kɔf]",
            "answer": "cough"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 19,
            "question": "[ðoʊ]",
            "answer": "though"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 20,
            "question": "[ðɪs]",
            "answer": "this"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 21,
            "question": "[koʊd]",
            "answer": "code"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 22,
            "question": "[kɑr]",
            "answer": "car"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 23,
            "question": "[frʌm]",
            "answer": "from"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 24,
            "question": "[bɑks]",
            "answer": "box"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 25,
            "question": "[groʊv]",
            "answer": "grove"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 26,
            "question": "[muv]",
            "answer": "move"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 27,
            "question": "[ʃʊk]",
            "answer": "shook"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 28,
            "question": "[rum]",
            "answer": "room"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 29,
            "question": "[stim]",
            "answer": "steam"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 30,
            "question": "[tʃiz]",
            "answer": "cheese"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 31,
            "question": "[lʌv]",
            "answer": "love"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 32,
            "question": "[lɔ]",
            "answer": "law"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 33,
            "question": "[dʒus]",
            "answer": "juice"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 34,
            "question": "[ritʃ]",
            "answer": "reach"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 35,
            "question": "[dʒɑb]",
            "answer": "job"
        }
    ]
}
{
    "level": "level3",
    "instructions": "Congratulations! You completed level 2! Follow the same winning process for Level 3. Be sure to finish the entire level to log your earned points for a competitive place on the leaderboards!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionNum": 1,
            "question": "[ˈæ.pəl]",
            "answer": "apple"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 2,
            "question": "[pəˈlis]",
            "answer": "police"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 3,
            "question": "[dʒɔɪ]",
            "answer": "joy"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 4,
            "question": "[ˈmju.zɪk]",
            "answer": "music"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 5,
            "question": "[əˈvɔɪd]",
            "answer": "avoid"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 6,
            "question": "[əˈpil]",
            "answer": "appeal"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 7,
            "question": "[əˈmjuz]",
            "answer": "amuse"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 8,
            "question": "[bɛg]",
            "answer": "beg"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 9,
            "question": "[ˈeɪ.prəl]",
            "answer": "April"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 10,
            "question": "[ˈbeɪʒ]",
            "answer": "beige"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 11,
            "question": "[ˈtrʌ.bəl]",
            "answer": "trouble"
        },        
        {
            "questionNum": 12,
            "question": "[ɛmˈplɔɪ]",
            "answer": "employ"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 13,
            "question": "[skaɪ]",
            "answer": "sky"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 14,
            "question": "[saʊnd]",
            "answer": "sound"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 15,
            "question": "[kloʊn]",
            "answer": "clone"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 16,
            "question": "[ˈraʊ.dɪ]",
            "answer": "rowdy"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 17,
            "question": "[ˈbɔɪ.lɪŋ]",
            "answer": "boiling"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 18,
            "question": "[flaɪt]",
            "answer": "flight"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 19,
            "question": "[ˈhɑ.kɪ]",
            "answer": "hockey"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 20,
            "question": "[koʊst]",
            "answer": "coast"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 21,
            "question": "[ðə]",
            "answer": "the"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 22,
            "question": "[ˈmʌ.ðɚ]",
            "answer": "mother"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 23,
            "question": "[ˈpeɪ.pɚ]",
            "answer": "paper"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 24,
            "question": "[ˈtrɛ.ʒɚ]",
            "answer": "treasure"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 25,
            "question": "[dəˈvɛ.lə.pɚ]",
            "answer": "developer"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 26,
            "question": "[ˈsɔft.wɛr]",
            "answer": "software"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 27,
            "question": "[brɪdʒ]",
            "answer": "bridge"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 28,
            "question": "[brið]",
            "answer": "breathe"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 29,
            "question": "[eksˈkjuz]",
            "answer": "excuse"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 30,
            "question": "[oʊˈʃən]",
            "answer": "ocean"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 31,
            "question": "[ɑkˈtoʊ.bɚ]",
            "answer": "October"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 32,
            "question": "[ˈneɪ.ʃən]",
            "answer": "nation"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 33,
            "question": "[ˈlæf.tɚ]",
            "answer": "laughter"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 34,
            "question": "[ˈdɪ.dʒə.təl]",
            "answer": "digital"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 35,
            "question": "[ˈkɑ.mə.dɪ]",
            "answer": "comedy"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 36,
            "question": "[ˈtʃɔɪ.səz]",
            "answer": "choices"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 37,
            "question": "[ˈdʒʌs.tə.faɪ]",
            "answer": "justify"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 38,
            "question": "[ˈtraɪ.əmf]",
            "answer": "triumph"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 39,
            "question": "[kənˈgræ.tjuˌleɪ.ʃənz]",
            "answer": "congratulations"
        },
        {
            "questionNum": 40,
            "question": "[aɪ pi eɪ]",
            "answer": "IPA"
        }
    ]
}